RANDALL PHARR

Richmond, VA 23228

Phone: (804) 240-9121 | Email: rpharr@richmond.edu

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kennon-p-064994190 | Github: https://github.com/krpharr

Portfolio: https://krpharr.github.io/fs-portfolio

SUMMARY

Web Engineer skilled in both front end and back end web programming with fourteen years background in higher education and thirty years in music performance. Integrity, dependability, work ethic, and collaboration are what I attribute to my career-long employer and client relationships. I enjoy working creatively and pragmatically in user interface and application design. In all aspects of Web Development such as Server-side Deployment, UI/UX design, JavaScript, and Databases, my mission is to deliver strong, dependable work in any role.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, ReactJS, JQuery, CSS, HTML, Python

Applications: Node.js, MySQL, MongoDB, Git, Materialize, Bootstrap, Visual Studio Code

PROJECTS

Box-Office Depot - Group Project

https://github.com/krpharr/box-office-depot https://krpharr.github.io/box-office-depot

- Browse information on movies and find showtimes and theaters by zip code.
- Built functionality to find movie showtimes by zip code and sort by movies and theaters.
- JavaScript, JQuery, Moment.js, Materialize, CSS, HTML, Github, OMDB API, Google Maps and Places API, TMS API

Weather Dashboard

https://github.com/krpharr/weather-dashboard https://krpharr.github.io/weather-dashboard

- Lookup weather conditions and 5-day forecast for any city in the world. Previous searches are displayed and updated with current conditions every five minutes.
- JavaScript, JQuery, Open Weather API, Moment.js, JQueryUI, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML

Code-Shotaun

https://github.com/krpharr/code-shotgun https://krpharr.github.io/code-shotgun

- Lookup weather conditions and 5-day forecast for any city in the world. Previous searches are displayed and updated with current conditions every five minutes.
- JavaScript, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML

EXPERIENCE

Adjunct Faculty 2011 – Present University of Richmond Richmond, VA

Jazz upright and electric bass private instruction and small jazz ensemble.

Adjunct Faculty
Virginia Commonwealth University

2005 – Present Richmond, VA

Jazz improvisation, jazz upright and electric bass private instruction, and small jazz ensembles.

Self-Employed1990 – PresentMusic ServicesRichmond, VA

Key Accomplishments:

- Santiago de Cuba Jazz Festival 2017
- Is You Is Or Is You Ain't My Baby with Bruce Hornsby soundtrack World's Greatest Dad
- Instructor Izmir International Jazz Camp Izmir, Turkey 2013
- The Kennedy Half Century WCVE Documentary

•

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Certificate: University of Richmond, Richmond VA

Six month intensive full-stack web technologies course in HTML, CSS, Javascript, AJAX, Node.js, ES6+, MySql, and ReactJS.

Jazz Studies Program: Virginia Commonwealth University 1988-1992